http://www.bodysupport.com/privacy-policy/

Last Updated: October 27, 2014
Body Support Systems, Inc. (BSS, Inc.) recognizes and respects the privacy rights of all visitors to our web site. The following privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your PII in accordance with our website.
What information do we collect from people that visit our blog or website?
We collect and store information that you provide to us through our website, at events, through our customer service representatives, marketing efforts, contests or promotions, or any other way we interact with you. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience. We may also maintain a record of your product interest and purchases. You may choose not to provide certain information, but you might not be able to to access all features of the website. For example, you must provide certain personal information in order to place an order through this website. When entering a contest or promotion, BSS, Inc. may again ask for the visitor's name, email address, billing address, shipping address, and phone number in order to notify winners or otherwise administer the contest.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, enter a contest or promotion, or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, fill out a form, enter a contest or promotion, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.• To improve our website in order to better serve you.• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.• To quickly process your transactions.• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect visitor information?
We use industry recognized security measures to protect your information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. Unfortunately, no transmission of information over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and therefore, we can not ensure or warrant the security of any information. Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We use cookies to:
• Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.• Keep track of advertisements.• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies, some features may be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We have implemented the following:
• Remarketing with Google AdSense• Google Display Network Impression Reporting• Demographics and Interests Reporting• DoubleClick Platform Integration
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
• Users can visit our site anonymously• Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.• Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.• Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page• Users are able to change their personal information by emailing us or by logging in to their account
How does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?We do allow third party behavioral tracking.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under 13 and do not intend to collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you should not provide any personal information to us and should use this website only with the permission and supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian and you suspect your child has provided personal information on or through our website, please contact us. Parental control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
• We will notify the users via email within 7 business days
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders• We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred
To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
• NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters• Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can
• Email us at  sales@bodysupport.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email to Unsubscribe
Consent / Terms of Use
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of information as descirbed above and agree to be legally bound by all the terms and conditions contained in the Terms of Use Agreement. Please read these terms carefully. By using this site you also represent that you are at least 18 years old, or you are at least the minimum legal age to enter into a contract in the jurisdiction in which you are viewing the site. In addition, when you use any current or future version of this site or any other bodysupport.com Web Site, you also will be subject to the terms and conditions of the Terms of Use Agreement. Please print a copy of this Terms of Use Agreement for your records.
We may, from time to time, modify the Terms of Use Agreement. When we make changes, we will post those changes here. Your use of the site following any such modification constitutes your agreement to the terms of the modified Terms of Use Agreement.
Contact Information
Body Support Systems, Inc. welcomes any questions, comments, or concerns about our privacy policy. You may contact us using the information below.
Online:www.bodysupport.comsales@bodysupport.com
By Mail:Body Support Systems, Inc.1040 Benson WayAshland, Oregon 97520 USA
